{
	"response_code": 0,
	"results": [
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How many SoC's we've all together?",
			"correct_answer": "28",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"14",
				"25",
				"18"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How many initial SoC's we have?",
			"correct_answer": "14",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"13",
				"28",
				"17"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How many additional SoC's we have?",
			"correct_answer": "14",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"11",
				"5",
				"28"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "How much percent is required for Health & Safety SoC?",
			"correct_answer": "100 %",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"97%",
				"80%",
				"75%"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What are the four steps of training?",
			"correct_answer": "Prepare, Present, Try out, Follow up",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Prepare, Practice, Precise, Check out",
				"Present, Try out, Learn, Follow up",
				"Prepare, Present, Try on, Follow down"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature of grill's upper platen?",
			"correct_answer": "218°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"177°C",
				"216°C",
				"70°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature of grill's lower platen?",
			"correct_answer": "177°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"75°C",
				"167°C",
				"218°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the internal temperature range for meat patties?",
			"correct_answer": "70-75°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"72-83°C",
				"177-218°C",
				"70-95°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the minimum internal temperature for meat patties?",
			"correct_answer": "70°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"72°C",
				"75°C",
				"63°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature range of grill's top platen?",
			"correct_answer": "210-230°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"218-230°C",
				"177-218°C",
				"130-175°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature range of grill's lower platen?",
			"correct_answer": "174-194°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"170-218°C",
				"100-150°C",
				"177-194°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature of the production bin?",
			"correct_answer": "63-66°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"60-65°C",
				"63°C",
				"66-70°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of the production bin?",
			"correct_answer": "30 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"40 min",
				"25 min",
				"15 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the holding time of production bin?",
			"correct_answer": "10 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"15 min",
				"20 min",
				"5 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature of universal toaster?",
			"correct_answer": "216±3°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"177±5°C",
				"215°C",
				"218±3°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the toasting cycle of universal toaster?",
			"correct_answer": "35±1 sec",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"37±1 sec",
				"216±3 sec",
				"35±3 sec"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of universal toaster?",
			"correct_answer": "30 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"15 min",
				"20 min",
				"45 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature of vertical toaster?",
			"correct_answer": "294°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"218°C",
				"194°C",
				"292°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the toasting cycle of vertical toaster?",
			"correct_answer": "17 sec",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"37 sec",
				"15 sec",
				"24 sec"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of vertical toaster?",
			"correct_answer": "30 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"35 min",
				"20 min",
				"10 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the heel height of Regular bun?",
			"correct_answer": "16mm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"18mm",
				"10mm",
				"26mm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the heel height of Big Mac bun?",
			"correct_answer": "16mm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"18mm",
				"10mm",
				"26mm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the heel height of Quarter bun?",
			"correct_answer": "16mm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"18mm",
				"10mm",
				"26mm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the diameter of Regular bun?",
			"correct_answer": "9.5-9.8cm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"9.6-9.8cm",
				"8.9-9.6cm",
				"5.2-7.3cm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the diameter of Big Mac bun?",
			"correct_answer": "9.5-9.8cm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"9.6-9.8cm",
				"8.9-9.6cm",
				"5.2-7.3cm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the diameter of Quarter bun?",
			"correct_answer": "9.5-9.8cm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"9.6-9.8cm",
				"8.9-9.6cm",
				"5.2-7.3cm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the overall height of Regular bun?",
			"correct_answer": "3.8-4.4cm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"3.4-4.4cm",
				"4.2-5.1cm",
				"3-4cm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the overall height of Big Mac bun?",
			"correct_answer": "5.7-6.4cm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"5.4-6.4cm",
				"4.2-5.1cm",
				"5-7cm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the overall height of Quarter bun?",
			"correct_answer": "3.8-4.4cm",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"3.4-4.4cm",
				"4.2-5.1cm",
				"3-4cm"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the four step complaint recovery?",
			"correct_answer": "Listen Apologize Solve the problem Thank you",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Listen Ask questions Sympathise Fix it",
				"Learn Apologize Save Try",
				"Listen Apologize Solve the riddle Thank me"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for fresh buns?",
			"correct_answer": "4 days",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"2 days",
				"10 days",
				"5 days"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for frozen buns?",
			"correct_answer": "28 days",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"26 days",
				"30 days",
				"48 days"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the secondary shelf life for frozen buns?",
			"correct_answer": "48 hours (included 2 hours defrost)",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"72 hours (included 2 hours defrost)",
				"24 hours (included 2 hours defrost)",
				"48 hours (included 4 hours defrost)"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature range for freezers?",
			"correct_answer": "<= -18°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"< -23°C",
				"> -5°C",
				"-18°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature range for chillers?",
			"correct_answer": "2-4°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"1-4°C",
				"2-7°C",
				"0-5°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the secondary shelf life of salads in chiller?",
			"correct_answer": "8 hours",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"6 hours",
				"4 hours",
				"12 hours"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the tempering time for tube sauces?",
			"correct_answer": "48 hours included 5 hours warmp up.",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"48 hours included 2 hours warm up.",
				"24 hours included 2 hours warm up.",
				"72 hours included 5 hours warm up."
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the tempering time for vegetables/bacon?",
			"correct_answer": "3 hours on grill area included 1 hour warm up.",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"2 hours on grill area included 1 hour warm up.",
				"4 hours on grill area included 2 hour warm up.",
				"3 hours on grill area included 2 hour warm up."
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the freeze down time of grillside freezers?",
			"correct_answer": "45 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"30 min",
				"25 min",
				"10 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of fryers?",
			"correct_answer": "45 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"30 min",
				"25 min",
				"15 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of UHC?",
			"correct_answer": "25 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"10 min",
				"35 min",
				"45 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of grills?",
			"correct_answer": "20 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"45 min",
				"30 min",
				"15 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of Muffin toaster?",
			"correct_answer": "15 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"20 min",
				"30 min",
				"45 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the warm up time of Steamer?",
			"correct_answer": "15 min",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"35 min",
				"20 min",
				"25 min"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the secondary shelf life of tortilla?",
			"correct_answer": "Unponeded: 4,5 days, opened: 1,5 days",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"Unponeded: 6 days, opened: 3 days",
				"Unponeded: 2,5 days, opened: 1 day",
				"Unponeded: 4,5 days, opened: 2,5 days"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the cooking temperature of chicken side fryers?",
			"correct_answer": "182°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"168°C",
				"172°C",
				"218°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the cooking temperature of fry station fryers?",
			"correct_answer": "168°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"178°C",
				"182°C",
				"177°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the steaming temperature of bacon?",
			"correct_answer": "176°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"178°C",
				"186°C",
				"152°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the steaming temperature of filet fish?",
			"correct_answer": "174°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"176°C",
				"177°C",
				"214°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the cooking time of fries?",
			"correct_answer": "180 sec",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"160 sec",
				"168 sec",
				"120 sec"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature of UHC?",
			"correct_answer": "93°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"79°C",
				"95°C",
				"83°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the temperature of UHC for breakfast?",
			"correct_answer": "79°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"63°C",
				"95°C",
				"77°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the cooking time of chicken patties and nuggets?",
			"correct_answer": "195 sec",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"180 sec",
				"197 sec",
				"174 sec"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the cooking time of legend patties and selects?",
			"correct_answer": "270 sec",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"250 sec",
				"120 sec",
				"230 sec"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the draw temperature of shake machine?",
			"correct_answer": "-3.2°C to -3.7°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"-3.4°C to -3.7°C",
				"-3.2°C to -3.8°C",
				"-3.0°C to -3.9°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the draw temperature of sundae machine?",
			"correct_answer": "-8°C to -9°C",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"-8°C to -10°C",
				"-2°C to -4°C",
				"-5°C to -8°C"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the weight of a sundae (without topping)?",
			"correct_answer": "141g",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"144g",
				"155g",
				"131g"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the weight of a mcflurry (without topping)?",
			"correct_answer": "155g",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"144g",
				"151g",
				"118g"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "McDonald's",
			"type": "multiple",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "What is the cooking time apple pies?",
			"correct_answer": "355 sec",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"255 sec",
				"300 sec",
				"360 sec"
			]
		}
	]
}